http://www.selectbreeders.com/s/privacy_policy

About
OverviewHistorySBS MissionWho is SBS?What Our Clients SayEmployment OpportunitiesContact Us
Florida
Peterson and Smith Equine Reproduction CenterRood and Riddle Equine HospitalWellGrove Equine Clinic
Kentucky
Hagyard Equine Medical InstituteRood and Riddle Equine Hospital
Ontario, Canada
Therion Science, Inc.
Oregon
Summit Equine, Inc.
Texas
6666 RanchSBSW / WSEH PartnershipWeatherford Equine Breeding Center
Italy
Centro di Riproduzione Equina CentauroStudio Veterinario Associato Luretta
Stallion Guide
Search StallionsAbout the SBS Stallion GuideHow Do I Post My Stallion to the Stallion Guide?
Resources
Informative Articles
Featured ArticlesAffiliate NewsBreeding with Frozen SemenContract ConsiderationsDisease and Health TestingEmbryo TransferFoal and Neonate CareFocus On Our BreedersFrozen SemenGeneral InterestGeneticsGuidelinesImport and ExportIndustry NewsMare ManagementNutritionStallion Management
Thawing InstructionsFAQ
FAQ
Contact
Privacy PolicyWebsite and NewsletterSelect Breeders Service, Inc. (SBS) will collect the following personal information on its website: name, address, phone number & email address via an optional online contact/inquiry form. The information is required to electronically submit the contact/inquiry form and subscribe to our free E-newsletter. An email address is also required when creating a user profile, enabling access to otherwise restricted information within the Knowledge Library and to participate in the messaging system incorporated into the SBS website. The personal data collected from this site will be used exclusively for the purpose of communicating information to the consumer about Select Breeders Service, Inc. and its Affiliate Laboratories. This information may be communicated via postal mail or email. Persons completing the online contact form will have the opportunity to select how they would like to be contacted by SBS. SBS and its Affiliated Laboratories will only contact the customer using the method(s) requested. Persons wishing to remove or correct their names and data from the SBS mailing lists should contact SBS directly via email or phone. Those receiving the SBS newsletter via email will have the opportunity to unsubscribe each time they receive an email newsletter. Once unsubscribed the email information will be removed from the SBS database. Personal data collected by SBS may be shared within the Select Breeders Services Network. For a list of Network laboratories click here. Personal data will not be shared, rented or sold to third parties outside the SBS Network. SBS Network Affiliates may have separate Privacy Policies thus information passed on to SBS Affiliates may be subject to different privacy standards.Business ServicesSBS requests all clients provide credit card information at the time of service. For frozen semen shipments payment is required in advance by credit card or personal check. Semen freezing and storage services clients have the option of paying their bill with the credit card on file, or being invoiced for the services provided. If the latter option is selected, SBS will retain credit card information and charge the credit card for any and all outstanding balances if payment has not been received within 30 days of invoicing. Select Breeders Service, Inc. will collect the following personal information for retention in our accounting software: name, address, phone number, email address, credit card number and expiration date. The personal data collected by SBS will be used exclusively for billing purposes and for communicating information to the consumer about Select Breeders Service, Inc. and its Affiliate Laboratories. This information may be communicated via postal mail or email. SBS clients will have the opportunity to select how they would like to be contacted by SBS.Select Breeders Service, Inc. complies with Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) practices when handling credit card information. All paper and electronic copies of credit card information are shredded or deleted respectively. Credit card information is only retained within our secure accounting software, which cannot be accessed by outside sources.All personal data is collected by Select Breeders Service, Inc., 961 Cayots Corner Rd., Chesapeake City, Maryland, 21915, USA. Telephone: 410-885-3202, info@selectbreeders.com.
Consumer complaints should be directed to the address and phone listed above.
